She calls me and I am satisfied with it, the
ownership of the trail comes to your skin, the ownership of Bandhan Awaaz is
in the hands of this industry, the
current level of Reliance on your skin,
or its employees, and in
view of the news, Daljeet Singh and have added a little from the toe cup, the
rest of the existence
is a reference that I welcome, I hope it will
rain a lot in Gurgaon,
Raghavendra,
I think it can be
seen, anyone can be,
so
if you want to
subscribe, don't forget to
subscribe, you can see a little correction in it, by
clicking a little above, then there is a
skin problem, I have been
from college, I work in the Railways,
when once in 2004
I brought such a thing on your skin, now after that, where the
days' infamy is more, a little price festival,
call me, six depends on
Nifty background 136 56, take it also, some
time ago you and on gas, many people
kept a comment on their body, moral spread, but
you covered that after the actual members
and I think, some time ago, see
what ITC ITC  There were comments from
Hafeez, however, in what I said, I
mentioned about the hotel business of ITC, if it has happened till now,
and we have seen the price performance of ITC quite
good in the last month
and the way we have seen the cost completion of these companies,
in the last one and a half months, if you have an opinion on Ras Mishri Bus, you will
add your point, you can see
that we see positive in some specific stocks,
where our
positive disruption is there,
click on it
and if not, we will
show from here, then till that improvement, my point is that
last
month's rally, so subscribe for this basic capacity, that is, from
one side to the
other, as
maintained under the management, it is not that if the
pressure increases today, then more clauses are cut, so till then we do
not do anything like this, the numbers and the country
wise, school remains, even in that,
tomato,
this entry which has been launched,
always remember the second thing
and it is for the
benefit of the combination, it should not be temporary
but will hit in the coming time.  So this
means that if you have
spent money,
I believe that this was the
reason, but if we talk about the
problem of the question, then wait a little, if problems start occurring then
after that we have to
look at the sector side for the portfolio.